welcome back to another audio editing
欢迎回到另一个音频编辑
tutorial using audacity in this video
本视频中使用Audacity的教程
we're going to learn how to record in
我们将学习如何在
some audio and we'll be looking at these
一些音频 我们将看到这些
different tools here up in the toolbar
工具栏上的不同工具
to make changes to that audio so to
对该音频进行更改以便
start I'm just going to record in a
开始我只是要在一个
simple audio file that we can edit
我们可以编辑的简单音频文件
testing testing 1 2 3 so again to do
测试测试%1%2%3再次这样做
that recording I just hit the record
那张唱片我刚出了名
button with my left mouse button and
用我的鼠标左键和
then when I'm done recording I
然后当我录完的时候
left-click on this square this stop
左键点击此方块即可停止
button if I want to play it back I can
按钮 如果我想回放它 我可以
just hit this green play button and
只需按下这个绿色的播放按钮
we'll play from the beginning if I want
如果我想的话我们从头开始玩
to pause at any point I can hit the
在任何时候暂停 我都可以按下
pause button to pause testing so I've
暂停按钮以暂停测试 以便我
paused now and now we see there's this
现在停顿了一下 现在我们看到了这个
black line right where I've paused
黑线就在我停顿的地方
that's how I know where I'm at in the
这就是我如何知道我在
recording you'll notice there's like a
录制的时候你会注意到有一种
this selection tool is currently
此选择工具当前
selected or pressed in we can change the
选中或按下 我们可以更改
tool by left clicking what tool we want
左键单击我们需要的工具即可使用该工具
to be on but right now we're on the
但现在我们正在
selection tool and that means it lets us
选择工具 这意味着它可以让我们
select or different portions of the
选择或不同的部分
audio so if I left click it'll move that
音频 所以如果我左键点击 它会移动
black line I'll stay there kind of where
黑线 我会呆在那里
the playhead is but the black line where
播放头只是黑线 在那里
I have my selection made is where it'll
我已经做出了我的选择 它将在哪里
start playing from if I hit play again
如果我再次点击播放 则从开始播放
so now if I hit playing it'll just play
所以现在如果我按下弹奏它就会弹奏
this the last thing I said which I
这是我说的最后一句话
believe was the number 3 3 and it'll
Believe是数字33 它会
play and then get to the end and stop if
播放 然后到达结尾 并在以下情况下停止
I want to play just a certain portion if
我只想扮演某个角色 如果
I want to start by saying 1 2 3 I can
我想从123I Can开始
click over here left click I get that
点击这里左键点击我明白了
black line to appear then I can click
出现黑色线条 然后我可以单击
play 1 2 3 it'll play just that portion
播放12 2 3它将只播放该部分
of the audio if I want to play back from
如果我想要从
the beginning these toggle moving to the
一开始 这些切换将移动到
beginning and end of the audio file so
音频文件So的开头和结尾
if I hit this button the playhead goes
如果我按下这个按钮 播放头就会
back to the beginning if I hit this
如果我击中了这个 回到开始
button it goes to the end that's kind of
按钮 一直到最后 这是一种
nice if you're working with a long video
如果你正在处理一段长视频 那就好了
file or if we're zoomed in very closely
文件或如果我们被非常近地放大
and we want to get to the end or the
我们想要走到最后或者是
beginning a lot of times I'll just click
开始很多次 我只会点击
the beginning and then play to make sure
开始 然后再玩 以确保
I play from the beginning because if
我从头开始打球是因为如果
I've been editing somewhere and I hit
我一直在编辑什么地方 然后我就
play I forget oh I don't want to be
玩我忘了 哦 我不想成为
playing from that portion I want to play
从我想要演奏的那部分开始演奏
from the beginning so that helps a lot
从一开始就能帮上很大忙
if we want to get rid of a certain
如果我们想摆脱某个特定的
portion let's say I only want to say
比方说我只想说
this isn't audio what did I say at the
这不是音频我刚才说什么来着
first testing testing let's say I want
首先测试 假设我想要
to get rid of my the first time I say
为了摆脱我的第一次我说
testing
测试
which is sort of this area here and to
这就是这片区域
verify that I can left-click and hold
验证我是否可以左击并按住
and select just those portions and now
只选择那些部分 现在
when I hit play it will only play what's
当我点击Play时 它将只播放
in this highlighted area testing and
在此突出显示的区域中测试和
then it just stops testing while that's
然后它就会停止测试 而这是
highlighted I can come up here to edit
突出显示我可以在此处进行编辑
and I can do some different things to it
我可以对它做一些不同的事情
I can cut I can copy I can delete if I
我可以剪切我可以复制我可以删除如果我
wanted I can duplicate which is like
想要我可以复制这就像
copy too but so if I just wanna delete
也复制 但如果我只想删除
it I just hit the hit delete right there
如果我刚刚点击了删除键
and now that's gone now I'm not saying
现在这一切都消失了 我不是说
testing there I'm saying only testing
在那里测试 我是说 只有测试
once instead of twice so I can go back
一次而不是两次 这样我就可以回去了
to the beginning and play testing one
一开始就玩测试一
two three if I wanted to come back I can
2 3 如果我想回来 我可以
go to edit and go undo delete and now
转到编辑并撤消删除 然后立即
that's done that's a undone I mean it's
已经完成了 这是未完成的 我的意思是
back now it's saying testing testing one
现在它说的是测试一个
two three if I want to and a quicker way
如果我想的话是二三 还有更快的方法
to delete if I want to delete just this
如果我只想删除此内容 请删除
portion I can just highlight it and hit
部分我只需突出显示并点击
the Delete key on my keyboard and it
键盘上的Delete键和它
goes away I can highlight everything and
离开后 我可以突出所有的东西
just hit delete and it all goes away if
只需按下删除 一切都会消失 如果
I had control Z it'll bring those back
我控制了Z 它会把那些带回来的
control Z's just like basically going at
Control Z基本上就像是在
it
它
undo it's just a shortcut key if I want
撤销它只是一个快捷键 如果我想的话
to select everything at once I can
一次选择所有我能选择的东西
double click and it selects everything
双击 它将选择所有内容
so let's say I had a really long
所以假设我有很长一段时间
recording I wanted the whole thing to be
录制我想要的整件事
selected just double click it selects it
选中只需双击即可选中
all and I can hit delete and now it's
所有人和我都可以点击删除 现在它是
gone I have nothing to get it back
我已经没有什么可以取回的了
edit undo and it comes back when things
编辑撤消 它将在以下情况下返回
are selected that's when you can apply
被选中 这是你可以申请的时候
effects to them also there's all these
对他们的影响还有所有这些
different effects we can do we can
我们可以做到的不同效果
amplify to increase the volume we can
放大我们可以增加的音量
add echo we can add some kind of fun
添加回声我们可以添加一些乐趣
effects or we can just apply some
效果 或者我们可以只应用一些
effects to make it more sound better and
效果让它听起来更好听
make us you know reduce some of the
让我们减少一些你知道的
noise and things like that we'll be
噪音和诸如此类的事情 我们会
doing that in future videos I want to
在未来的视频中 我想这样做
talk about some of these different tools
谈谈其中一些不同的工具
here so if I want to zoom in on where I
在这里 如果我想要放大我
say 1 2 3 I want to zoom in closer on
比方说1 2 3我想放大一些
one of those sound waves I can actually
其中一种声波 我实际上可以
click this zoom tool here so I left
点击这里的缩放工具 我离开了
click on it and then if I left click
点击它 然后如果我左键点击
anywhere that I left click on my WAV
在我离开的任何地方点击我的WAV
file or my wave view down here it'll
文件或我的波视图在这里它将
zoom in and I can see what these are
放大看 我能看到这些是什么
looking like if I right click it'll zoom
看起来就像我右击它就会放大
out and left click will zoom in
缩小并左键单击将放大
so I can zoom way out so it's just
所以我可以把它缩小 所以它只是
looking like that I can zoom way in and
看起来像这样我可以放大和
now I'm into like incredibly incredibly
现在我喜欢上了难以置信的不可思议的
granular so I'll come out here and zoom
所以我会来到这里 放大
out and we can see we can see exactly
我们可以看到我们可以准确地看到
what this part of the audio is so to
音频的这一部分是什么
play from a certain point I have to go
从某一点开始打球 我必须离开
back to my selection tool and then click
返回到我的选择工具 然后单击
in here and click play one so that's me
在这里 点击Play One 这就是我
saying 1 1 2 3 if I want to let's say I
说1 1 2 3如果我想说
want to move over and see what's
我想过去看看有什么
happening earlier in the audio I can
在音频中发生的更早 我可以
come down to the bottom and use this
到最底层来 用这个
slider to view to move around and see
使用滑块查看可四处移动并查看
different points of the audio I can also
不同的音频点我也可以
hold down that can I do that now maybe
按住那个 我现在可以这样做吗？
not I thought I could hold down the
不是的 我以为我能按住
mouse middle mouse button but I guess
鼠标中键 但我想
not and I can I can use this slider and
不 我可以 我可以使用这个滑块
I can also if I want to move so this
我也可以 如果我想搬家的话
just changes the way that I'm looking at
只是改变了我看待问题的方式
the audio if I actually want to move it
如果我真的想移动它 音频
to a different point I can come and zoom
到一个不同的点 我可以来放大
out here let's say I want to move this
在这里 假设我想要移动这个
whole portion forward I can click this
整个部分向前 我可以点击这个
tool at a time shift tool and that lets
工具一次移动工具 并让
me actually move the audio so right now
实际上 我现在就移动音频
it was starting at 0 seconds and it was
它是从0秒开始的 它是
playing until about 4 seconds I can tell
玩到大约4秒 我能看出来
by looking at the top of the timeline
通过查看时间线的顶部
here but if I want to move it and have
在这里 但如果我想移动它并拥有
empty space for the first second of
第一秒的空格
audio I can do that by just left
音频 我只要离开就可以做到
clicking and dragging the audio and now
点击并拖动音频 现在
if I go back to the beginning and hit
如果我回到起点 打出
play it'll be silent for a second and
播放一下 静默一秒钟 然后
then my audio will start testing testing
然后我的音频将开始测试测试
and so it's actually it really is
所以它实际上是真的
actually complete silence and then you
实际上完全沉默 然后你
kind of hear this little tiny bit of
有点像是听到了这个小小的
noise as it comes in possibly so this is
可能会有噪音 所以这是
the time shift to when it's how to move
时间转换到如何移动的时间
around I wanted to show you one more
我想再给你看一次
thing I actually cleared out that audio
我真的把那段音频清空了
but one more tool I wanted to show you
但我想向你们展示的另一个工具
is that we can bring in some audio so if
我们可以引入一些音频 所以如果
we just go we can actually drag and drop
我们只要走 我们实际上可以拖放
so if we bring in some music like I have
所以如果我们带来一些像我这样的音乐
this this is like a WAV file as jazz
这个就像是爵士乐的wav文件
guitar we go properties it's a dot wave
吉他 我们去财产 这是一个点波
I can just left click and drag and drop
我只需左键单击和拖放即可
this in here and it imports the audio
这个在这里 它导入音频
just like that
简单得不得了
we can also go file and then we go to
我们也可以去归档 然后我们去
import and we can import an audio and
导入 我们可以导入音频和
actually import it in MIDI files as well
实际上也可以在MIDI文件中导入
and we'll show them in denotation then
然后我们将以外延的形式展示它们
something I want to show with this this
我想用这个来展示一些东西
last tool is if we hover over and look
最后一个工具是如果我们悬停并查看
this is the envelope tool and we can
这是信封工具 我们可以
left-click on it and it creates sort of
左键单击它 它会创建一种
some gray lines across the top or like a
一些横跨顶部的灰线或类似于
lighter gray in the middle what it lets
中间是较浅的灰色 它允许
us do is if we just click one point if
我们所做的是 如果我们只点击一个点 如果
we left click and hold we can move up
我们左键点击并按住 我们可以向上移动
and down and control the volume and make
调低音量 控制音量 让
this very soft or much louder so now if
这个声音非常柔和或更响亮 所以如果
we play this it's what it sounds like we
我们演奏这首曲子 就像我们听起来那样
can actually have it fade in by clicking
可以通过点击将其淡入
over here and choosing a second point so
在这里选择第二个点
now if we left click here we can
现在如果我们离开点击这里 我们可以
actually make this much softer and we
实际上让它变得更柔软
can move this and have it kind of fade
可以移动它 让它褪色
in loud we can click another point here
我们可以在这里点击另一个点
and make it kind of soft so we can have
把它弄得柔软些 这样我们就可以
that be loud and then just drop down to
声音很大 然后下降
soft automatically and so that's the
自动变软 所以这就是
envelope tool to just adjusting volume
信封工具 以调整音量
it kind of creates this envelope around
它就像是在
all the audio and you can adjust very
所有的音频 你可以调整
quickly the audio levels at certain
很快 音频水平在某些
points in the wave so that's basically
所以基本上
it for the the tools up here that I
为了这些工具
wanted to cover for today appreciate you
我想替今天的班谢谢你
watching and I'll catch you in the next
我会在下一个时间找你的
video
视频